Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-2013 and undated; 6
  - ILGWU Join In Everybody, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-070)
  - ILGWU Labor Day :60, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-071)
  - ILGWU Labor Day :60, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-072)
  - ILGWU Lillian :60, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-073)
  - ILGWU Labaor Day spots, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-074)
    Traditional; Traditional/Inversion; Look for the Union Label; Combination with intro; Harmonica soloed; Harmonica :12
  - ILGWU spots, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-075)
    664 Look Good; 665 Easter Parade
  - ILGWU spots, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-076)
  - ILGWU spots, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-077)
  - ILGWU Money Memo; Union Label, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-078)
  - ILGWU Mothers and Families, 1991 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-079)
  - ILGWU Music, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-080)
    Union Label; Join In Everybody; Join In orchestral version; We Make Jobs
  - ILGWU New radio mix chorus III :39.6, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-081)
  - ILGWU New radio mix chorus III :39.6, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-082)
  - ILGWU New radio mix chorus III :39.6, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-083)
  - ILGWU New radio mix chorus III :39.6, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-084)
  - ILGWU radio, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-085)
    Norma "Taller de Union" :20; Ana Luisa "Familias" :20; Laura "Beneficias" :20; Orchestra and chorus, solo
  - ILGWU Original Chorus, 1982 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-086)
  - ILGWU PACE reference copy, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-087)
  - ILGWU PACE "Hotline" :60 #676, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-088)
  - ILGWU PACE "Hotline" :60 #676, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-089)
  - ILGWU PACE "Hotline" :60 #676, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-090)
  - ILGWU PACE "Women of DuBois", 1989 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-091)
  - ILGWU One Day at a Time; Look for the Union Label, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-092)
  - ILGWU Puerto Rico, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-093)
    Orchestra and chorus; Orchestra alone; Anna Luisa; Norma; Laura
  - ILGWU Puerto Rico, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-094)
  - ILGWU Rally 2x:60, 1983 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-095)
  - ILGWU Report to Convention Zohra Lampert voiceover, 1989 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-096)
  - ILGWU Rally "Uncontrolled" :60, 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-097)
  - ILGWU Union Label song Spanish version by Tony Lespier, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-098)
  - ILGWU Union Label Week spot 2 (fast) :30, AFL-CIO Food and Beverage Workers, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-099)
  - ILGWU Veto 671; Washington Veto 672, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-100)
  - ILGWU Veto 671; Washington Veto 672, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-101)
  - ILGWU Voting 667 :30, 1984 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-102)
  - ILGWU Voting 667 :30, 1984 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-103)
  - ILGWU Washington Veto 672, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-104)
  - ILGWU Washington Veto 672, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-105)
  - Jerusalem Post: Listening Post 681, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-106)
  - Jerusalem Post: Listening Post 681, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-107)
  - Jocomo scratch track, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-108)
  - Ken Prewitt Business News, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-109)
  - Life Extention Institute: Extraordinary Place 679 Mintz, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-110)
  - Life Extention Institute 675 :60, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-111)
  - Long Island Trust, WCBS, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-112)
  - Marse Fields, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-113)
    Grace Garland; Abra Bigham; Joan Rosenfels; Zelda Puliam; Allison Held
  - Marval Demo Easter radio 3x:60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-114)
    Fresh turkey promos: A Letter; My Goodness; I Have Tasted
  - Marval Poulry, 1979 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-115)
    My Goodness MVL-644
  - Mike Sanyour, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-116)
  - Miss Paula Green, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-117)
  - Music miscellaneous, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-118)
    Look of Love; Taste of Honey; By the Time I Get to Phoenix; Sunny; Windmills; Feeling Groovy; What the World Needs Now; Who Am I; All My Laughter
  - Monty Pizza, 1980 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-119)
  - New York Post: Mr. District Attorney 613 :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-120)
  - New York Times auditions first series, 1970 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-121)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-122)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-123)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-124)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-125)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-126)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-127)
  - New York Times Home Delivery :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-128)
  - New York Times Home Delivery spoken demo, 1975 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-129)
  - New York Times piano, words, music, 1975 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-130)
  - New York Times Home Delivery preliminary :10 two versions, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-131)
  - New York Times Sunday Home Delivery 584 :60, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-132)
  - New York Times; Subaru spots, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-133)
    Tammy; Blue Collar; Home Delivery; Subaru Key; Wheels; Women's Wagon; Travelling VO
  - New York Times: Tammy Sings, 1982 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-134)
    Got My Family Life; I Am On My Way
  - Norman Kasow Music, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-135)
  - Oh Dear: First Tries, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-136)
  - Paramount Chickens, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-137)
    Buying Chickens; Six Chickens
  - Patco Resources radio spots, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-138)
    Barbara Cartland; The Formula; Havioline Supreme Motor Oil; Children of the Lion
  - Patco Sampler, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-139)
    Moods; Instrumental colors; Ethnic; Styles; Statement
  - Peggy Courtney radio reel, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-140)
    New York Times: Margaret Mary; Blue Collar; Public Health Service: Dog; William; Subaru: The Key; Snowstorm; Marval; Cardio Fitness; Tsing Tao
  - Radio Smithsonian: Images of Labor, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-141)
  - Radio Success Stories vol. 2, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-142)
  - Singing exercises, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-143)
  - Stanley: I'm a Stanley Woman original demo, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-144)
  - Stanley: I'm a Stanley Woman original demo, 1982 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-145)
  - Stanley: Stanley Woman, 1982 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-146)
  - Subaru spots, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-147)
    Horns :30; Hoofbeats :30
  - Subaru spots, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-148)
    Key; Wheels; Woman; Music; Instrumental; Music with vocal
  - Subaru/New York Times 14 spots, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-149)
  - State of Israel Bonds, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-150)
  - State of Israel Bonds #3, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-151)
  - State of Israel Bonds #3, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-152)
  - State of Israel Bonds One Week Only, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-153)
  - State of Israel Bonds second commercial, Undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-154)
  - State of Israel Bonds 3 cities: New York, Dallas, Philadelphia, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-155)
  - State of Israel Bonds 6 1/2% :60, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-156)
  - State of Israel Bonds 6 1/2% :60, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-157)
  - State of Israel Bonds 7 1/2% :60, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-158)
  - State of Israel Bonds 7 1/2% :60, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-159)
  - State of Israel Bonds airchecks 14:22, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-160)
  - State of Israel Bonds airchecks 14:22, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-161)
  - State of Israel Bonds drive 2, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-162)
    New York; Philadelphia; Washington; Dallas; Chicago
  - State of Israel Bonds Elie Wiesel, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-163)
  - State of Israel Bonds Elie Wiesel master, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-164)
  - State of Israel Bonds Elie Wiesel, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-165)
  - State of Israel Bonds Elie Wiesel #685, 1992 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-166)
  - State of Israel Bonds Elie Wiesel #685, 1992 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-167)
  - State of Israel Bonds "Ethiopia", Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-168)
  - State of Israel Bonds "Ethiopia", Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-169)
  - State of Israel Bonds "Ethiopia", Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-170)
  - State of Israel Bonds "They Are Waiting" #684, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-171)
  - State of Israel Bonds "They Are Waiting" #684, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-172)
  - State of Israel Bonds WINS, 1991 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-173)
  - Sterling Bank 60th Anniversary #677, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-174)
  - Sterling Bank 60th Anniversary #677, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-175)
  - Sterling Bank 60th Anniversary #677, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-176)
  - Sterling Bank "Anticipate Change" :60 #690, 1995 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-177)
  - Sterling Bank "Anticipate Change" :60 #690, 1995 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-178)
  - Sterling Bank B-alternate, 1986 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-179)
  - Sterling Bank B-alternate, 1986 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-180)
  - Sterling Bank: Capelli interview WBBR, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-181)
  - Sterling Bank "Consolidation" :60 #691, 1996 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-182)
  - Sterling Bank "Consolidation" :60 #691, 1996 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-183)
  - Sterling Bank "Cutting Staff" #692, 1996 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-184)
  - Sterling Bank "Cutting Staff" #692, 1996 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-185)
  - Sterling Bank "Doors" :60, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-186)
  - Sterling Bank "Doors" :60, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-187)
  - Sterling Bank "Hometown" 688, 1993 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-188)
  - Sterling Bank "Hometown" 688, 1993 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-189)
  - Sterling Bank "Hometown 2" 689, 1993 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-190)
  - Sterling Bank "Money to Lend" #679, 1990 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-191)
  - Sterling Bank "Money to Lend" #679, 1990 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-192)
  - Sterling Bank "New Spirit" #687, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-193)
  - Sterling Bank "New Spirit" #687, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-194)
  - Sterling Bank radio :60, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-195)
  - Sterling Bank radio :60 #688, 1993 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-196)
  - Sterling Bank "Sound Business" #686, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-197)
  - Sterling Bank "Sterling on Seventh" promo, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-198)
  - Sterling Bank "Substantial Business 2" #674, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-199)
  - Subaru/New York Times 14 spots, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-200)
  - Subaru/New York Times 14 spots, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-201)
  - Sunday Morning radio Toronto: American Labour Movement/AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-202)
  - Sterling Bank "Substantial Business 2" #674, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-203)
  - U.S. Public Health Service: Smoking and health announcements "Scorecard" 2x:60, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-204)
  - U.S. Public Health Service: Women and Smoking, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-205)
  - U.S. Public Health Service spots, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-206)
    Young man/old man :55; Young woman :30; Gonna Tell You Somethin' :30
  - WCBS-AM Newss 88 aircheck; First Women's Bank, 1989 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-207)
  - Wickes take 15, Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-208)
  - WOR-TV News at Noon, 1978 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-209)
  - X "Soggy", Undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-210)
  - Al Marlins and Sy Peck re-dubs, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-001)
  - Alan Oser, Real Estate Editor, 1972 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-002)
  - Alan Truscott, 1973 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-003)
  - Bill Honan, sides 1 and 2, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-004)
  - Cardio-Fitness auditions, John Bentley cont'd, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-005)
  - Cardio-Fitness auditions, Ken Campbell, John Bentley, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-006)
  - Dave Anderson interview tapes, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-007)
  - Ernesto Gasco arias, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-008)
  - Freeze 'Ems Kids' voiceover fruit sequence, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-009)
  - Freeze 'Ems revised voiceover, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-010)
  - ILGWU 7 spots, 1979 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-011)
    Norma :60; Emma :60; Meredith :60; Isabelle :60 (Spanish); Chorus music only; Norma Taller de Union Chorus III; Carmen Chorus III
  - ILGWU English and Spanish spots FX, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-012)
    Bus pass by; Clicks; Heavy Traffic; Medium Traffic
  - ILGWU Isabelle :60 #648, 1979 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-013)
  - ILGWU Report to Convention II master, 1989 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-014)
  - ILGWU Report to Convention voice dub, 1989 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-015)
  - ILGWU Report to Convention voice original, 1989 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-016)
  - ILGWU Spanish client tape, 1980 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-017)
  - ILGWU spots, 1991 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-018)
    Judy and Jamin; Susan; Ramona
  - ILGWU Vancile, 1980 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-019)
  - ILGWU voice tracks, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-020)
    Ramona; Susan; Judy; Judy and Jamin
  - ILGWU We Make Jobs :30, 1992 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-021)
  - Jill Faust part 1, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-022)
  - Jill Faust part 2, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-023)
  - Jill Faust original interview, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-024)
  - Joe Durso, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-025)
  - John Leonard, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-026)
  - John Leonard, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-027)
  - Leonard Koppett interview tapes, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-028)
  - Marval Poultry: Arlen Dean Snyder voiceovers for Pledge and Parts, 1981 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-029)
  - Marval Poultry #1 back-up audio, 1982 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-030)
  - Marval Poultry #2 FT mono, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-031)
  - Marval Poultry: Kevin Conway, Mila Barnett, 1981 (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-032)
  - Max Frankel, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-033)
  - Max Frankel, Undated (Box AV29, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-034)
  - New York Times--Ada Louise Huxtable, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-035)
  - New York Times--Alan Truscott, 1973 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-036)
  - New York Times--Alan Truscott, 1973 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-037)
  - New York Times--Bill Honan, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-038)
  - New York Times--Bill Honan, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-039)
  - New York Times--Bill Honan, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-040)
  - New York Times--Bill Honan original interviews, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-041)
  - New York Times--Clive Barnes, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-042)
  - New York Times--Dan Schwarz, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-043)
  - New York Times--John Canady interview, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-044)
  - New York Times--John O'Connor reel 1, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-045)
  - New York Times--John O'Connor reel 1, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-046)
  - New York Times--Max Frankel, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-047)
  - New York Times--Max Frankel, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-048)
  - New York Times--Sy Peck, Arts and Leisure Editor, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-049)
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby reel 1, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-050)
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby reel 1, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-051)
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby reel 2, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-052)
  - New York Times--Vincent Canby reel 2, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-053)
  - Sterling Bank--Substantial Business A-master, 1986 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-054)
  - Sterling Bank--Doors :60, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-055)
  - Week in Review: Robert Clurman #1, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-056)
  - Week in Review: Robert Clurman #2, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-057)
  - Will Weng, Puzzle Editor, 1972 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-058)
  - ILGWU Vancile, 1980 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-059)
  - New York Times--Standby :60 with Tammy Grimes, 1975 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-060)
  - ILGWU--An American Christmas, 1984 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-061)
  - ILGWU--An American Christmas, 1983 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-062)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day, 1983 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-063)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day, 1983 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-064)
  - ILGWU--Rally 1 and 2, 1983 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-065)
  - ILGWU--Veto, 1986 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-066)
  - ILGWU--Veto, 1986 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-067)
  - ILGWU--Voting, 1984 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-068)
  - ILGWU--Voting, 1984 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-069)
  - New York Times--Heidi Linder, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-070)
  - New York Times--Mr. District Attorney, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-071)
  - New York Times--4 spots, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-072)
    Jim Roach Sunday Features; Jim Roach Sportswriters; Dress Dress; Al Marlins Travel
  - New York Times--Sunday Home Delivery #584, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-073)
  - New York Times--Sunday Home Delivery #584, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-074)
  - Subaru--Hoofbeats, Horns, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-075)
  - Subaru--Radio spots, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-076)
  - Subaru--Radio spots, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-077)
  - Subaru--Radio spots, Undated (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-078)
  - Tony Schwartz on T.V. News WQXR, 1981 (Box AV30, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-079)
  - Alan Oser, Joe Durso scratch track, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-080)
  - Cardio-Fitness Centers--This Morning :60, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-081)
  - Cardio-Fitness Centers--This Morning :60, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-082)
  - Cardio-Fitness Centers--Yourself, Your Friends :60, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-083)
  - Compilation tape, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-084)
    William PHS; Gonna Tell You Something PHS; Young and Female PHS; Home Delivery Music NYT
  - Goya #1, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-085)
  - Goya #2, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-086)
  - Goya #3, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-087)
  - Goya--Coco Goya 657 Hermione :60, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-088)
  - Goya--Coco Goya Mixers full demo, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-089)
  - Goya--Coco Goya Mixers full demo, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-090)
  - Goya--Coco Goya Mixers Island version 673, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-091)
  - Goya--Coco Goya Mixers Island version 673, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-092)
  - Goya--Coco Goya Mixers music no announcer, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-093)
  - Goya--Mila Add 'Ems, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-094)
  - Goya--Sazon SR#1, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-095)
  - Goya--Sazon SR#2, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-096)
  - Goya--Sazon SR#3, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-097)
  - Goya--Sazon SR#4, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-098)
  - Goya--Sazon SR#5, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-099)
  - ILGWU, 1980 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-100)
  - ILGWU--Chorus, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-101)
  - ILGWU--Easter Parade 665, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-102)
  - ILGWU--Easter Parade 665, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-103)
  - ILGWU--Easter Parade 665, 1986 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-104)
  - ILGWU--Interview Radio KALI, 1977 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-105)
  - ILGWU--Join In Everybody, 1992 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-106)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day 661, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-107)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day 661, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-108)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day 666, 1984 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-109)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day spots, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-110)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day spots, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-111)
  - ILGWU--Labor Day spots, 1983 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-112)
    America the Beautiful; Look for the Union Label; Oh Beautiful
  - ILGWU--Lexicon Chorus III national recording, 1988 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-113)
  - ILGWU--Lood for the Union Label :25, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-114)
  - ILGWU--Look for the Union Label entire song, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-115)
  - ILGWU--Look for the Union Label entire song, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-116)
  - ILGWU--Look for the Union Label and other spots, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-117)
  - ILGWU--Mothers and Families, 1991 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-118)
  - ILGWU--Mothers and Families, 1991 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-119)
  - ILGWU--Music, Undated (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-120)
  - ILGWU--New radio mix Chorus III #653, 1984 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-121)
  - ILGWU--New radio mix Chorus III #653, 1984 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-122)
  - ILGWU--New radio mix Chorus III #653, 1984 (Box AV31, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-123)
  - ILGWU--On Stage II, Undated (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-124)
  - ILGWU--PACE Hotline #676, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-125)
  - ILGWU--PACE Hotline #676, 1988 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-126)
  - ILGWU--PACE Voices of DuBois, 1989 (Box AV32, Audio-reel RL11500-RR-127)